worksheetworks.com 2011-12-25

# WorksheetWorks.com

The WorksheetWorks.com Privacy Policy

WorksheetWorks.com respects each individual's right to personal privacy. We will collect and use information through our web site only in the ways disclosed in this statement. This statement applies solely to information collected at WorksheetWorks.com?s web site.

## I. Information Collection

WorksheetWorks.com uses only standard data collection methods for statistical purposes. This information includes your ip address, browser type and language preference, We collect demographic data in order to better understand where our users are, what language they prefer and what software they use to view the website. We also collect names and email addresses which are voluntarily given to us through feedback mechanisms in order to provide responses to questions. WorksheetWorks.com never knowingly ask a child under 13 to divulge personal information.

WorksheetWorks.com employs cookies in order to trace user actions from one page to the next. This is necessary in order for the site's basic functionality to work. A cookie is a small text file that our Web server places on a user?s computer hard drive to be a unique identifier. Some of our cookies have expiration dates, while others do not, but none of the cookies collect personally identifiable information.

## II. Information Usage

The information collected by WorksheetWorks.com will be used exclusively for internal purposes which include usage statistics, plans for additional languages and geographically relevant content, and email announcements. Users who provide information may, at their option, receive updates about website changes and new additions via email.

WorksheetWorks.com will not sell or otherwise disclose user data to third parties for any reason or purpose. In addition, user data will not be supplemented by data from other sources. Out of respect for the privacy of our users we will purge any personally identifying data on request.

Some pages on WorksheetWorks.com contain links to other websites. These outside websites may have privacy policies that differ significantly from our own.

If our policy on information collection or uses changes, this privacy policy will be updated to accurately reflect those changes.

## III. Access to Information

WorksheetWorks.com does not provide access to any user information, even your own, as we have no way to verify your identity. At your request (through email or the contact page), we will delete your personally identifiable information from any and all databases.

## IV. Problem Resolution

If problems arise, users may contact WorksheetWorks.com through the contact page on the website. We are committed to resolving disputes wherever possible within three business days.

## V. Data Storage and Security

WorksheetWorks.com protects user information by storing it in a secure, offline location. Personally identifying user data is secured at the point it is submitted and transmitted off of the application server at frequent intervals. Please note that your connection to the web server itself is not secure and your transmission may be captured at any time.

|   | 

## Adobe Reader

The worksheets on this site are created in PDF format. To view and print PDF files, you need the free Acrobat Reader. If you don't have it, you can get it [here](http://www.adobe.com/products/acrobat/readstep2.html).

Find more great educational websites at these two major content portals.

**Public Beta Preview**

This website is currently in the late stages of its development, a state referred to as _beta_. As with all beta software, it has some quirks and many parts are not yet available. We are working hard to finalize the system's structure, and roughly once every two weeks we roll out new functionality towards this goal. Until then you may notice that some resources move or even disappear for a while.  
  
---|---|---
